What a perseverance friend Ratika ji come here for
a minute please come how do you get the Young
Agent of the Year award for two years and that too back to
back Latika ji how do you do it,
for that you don't have to meet the client,
this is not a service from home,
understood oh madam it is not necessary to meet the client every time
ok video call
can also be done learn to work smart you never miss a chance to
pull each other's leg ma'am this is the way ma'am
always starts ko g come on guy I am leaving I'll see you guy
where are you friend hey
sit the atmosphere is getting ready not today today is a heavy
movie night no night yes
movie night with mom I mean yes friend
mom loved watching movies but
because of household responsibilities and my studies
she had to leave it all so it just didn't
feel good so we decided every Saturday we will
sit together and watch movies wow amazing this is what they
call responsible children be like this
exactly I
am responsible brother from before hey  Wait
friend, 10 minutes are left for
taking a selfie, okay wait a second, don't delay friend
[Music]
photo, thank you ma'am, I had come to take a cold drink, I do
n't know, I need cold
drink
chips, right, I do
n't know where
[Music]
you are also there, it's okay, I am also there, I
can understand, there is grief of the past too
[Music]
Mom must be feeling very proud, wherever you are,
you are also there,
someone is with you, someone is standing with you
[Music]